goldsgym.com 2014-06-25

# Gold's Gym | Privacy Policy | Fitness Gym

Gold’s Gym is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors and has prepared the following statement to inform users how personally identifying information and non-personally identifying information is gathered from our Web site and used by GOLDSGYM.COM. GOLD’S GYM encourages its Web site users to be smart about choosing when, and to whom, to release information online.

**PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES**  
Whenever our Privacy Policy is modified we will notify you that changes have been made by updating the month, day, and year currently displayed beside the link to our privacy policy statement. This link is located at the bottom of each page within the GOLDSGYM.COM Web site.

**CHILDREN**  
Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Web site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this Web site in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

**NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
Certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors is collected by the standard operation of GOLDSGYM.COM’s internet servers and through the use of “cookie” technology (as described below), such as the type of internet browser you are using and the domain name of your internet service provider, where you go within the Web site, how much time you spend in any particular area and what you buy.

**COOKIES**  
A “cookie” is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. All Web sites on GOLDSGYM.COM where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable by you require that you accept cookies. Generally, we use cookies to:

  * Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service. This cookie is set when you register or “Sign In” and is modified when you “Sign Out” of our services. GOLDSGYM.COM also uses cookies to store your zip code for other services, such as facilitating your finding a GOLD’S GYM near you via the Web site.
  * Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing GOLDSGYM.COM is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, usage by a registered user versus by an unregistered user, and to help target messages, promotions and ads based on user interests and behavior.
  * Assist us in tracking visits to and business at our store, and to process the items in your shopping basket. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called “clickstream” or “click trail” and may also describe which pages you have seen in each part of the store.
  * Track your progress and number of entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes and contests. When a GOLD’S GYM -hosted promotion uses cookies, the information written to the cookie indicates the player’s progress through the promotion, and may be used to track entries, submissions, and status in prize drawings.
  * Measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of the GOLDSGYM Web site you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand how our users’ habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on GOLD’S GYM.COM a better one. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our Web sites.

Advertisers that serve ads onto GOLD’S GYM.COM may also use their own cookies. You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Web site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications. You may make changes to your notification preferences at any time.

You have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those GOLDSGYM.COM services that require registration in order to participate. These services include (but are not limited to): participating in any loyalty or incentive programs, signing up for free passes, etc.

Information collected by the standard operation of GOLDSGYM.COM ‘s internet servers and through the use of cookies is analyzed by GOLD’S GYM only in aggregate form and is used to improve the content of our Web site, to tailor the content and/or layout to consumer trends and to notify users about updates to the Web site. GOLD’S GYM reserves the right to disclose or otherwise utilize this information in aggregate form, for any purpose, in its sole judgment.

Log data collected on web servers both within GOLDSGYM.COM’s control and under the confidential control of GOLDSGYM.COM’s third party ad service provider(s) supplies GOLD’S GYM with aggregate information about the number of visits to different pages on our Web site. This information is not personally identifiable information and is used by GOLD’S GYM to improve the content of our Web site.

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**  
GOLD’SGYM.COM receives and stores any personally identifiable information you enter on our Web site or provide to us in any other way (such as your name, street address, telephone number and email address). Also, if you contact GOLD’S GYM Online, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Such information is only known to GOLD’S GYM when it is voluntarily submitted or posted to us. Wherever GOLDSGYM.COM collects personally identifiable information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

Personally identifiable information will be used by GOLD’S GYM and its authorized agents only: (1) to process your requests (e.g., register you for a contest or sweepstakes or fulfill your merchandise order); (2) to communicate with you or personalize the Web site based on your stated interests and preferences or make related offers to you; (3) to administer the Web site or serve you when you have questions or problems; and/or (4) as may, in GOLD’S GYM’s sole judgment, be required by any applicable laws, rules or regulations or the Terms and Conditions applicable to this Web site.

Personally identifiable information will only be shared with third parties to further the purpose for which you provide such information (e.g., to process your subscription request, enrollment registration or merchandise order) or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights of GOLD’S GYM or its affiliates or subscribers.

If GOLD’S GYM intends to disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in circumstances not outlined above, you will be advised at the time that we request that you provide us such information, such as in the rules of a sweepstakes or contest or as part of the terms of a given promotion, and you will be provided with the opportunity to opt out of our online database so that participation in the registration, sweepstakes, contest or other activity is possible without disclosing personally identifiable information to such third parties. GOLD’S GYM does not currently sell any personally identifiable information to third parties.

**SHOPPING SERVICES**  
GOLD’S GYM strives to offer its visitors a secure and safe environment for credit card purchases. Some of the shopping and fulfillment services offered on GOLDSGYM.COM may be operated by third party shopping partners.

They collect personally identifiable information necessary to accept, process and ship your ordered merchandise on behalf of GOLD’S GYM to provide you with information you may request and updates on the status of your order, and to assist your purchasing experience. Our shopping partners collect personally identifiable information from you by “active” means, whereby you actively give our shopping partners, as GOLDSGYM.COM’s agents, that information when ordering merchandise.

Personally identifiable information entered into any of the GOLDSGYM.COM shopping services is used only to complete your transaction and never revealed to others or used by our shopping partners for any purpose not authorized by GOLD’S GYM. Our shopping partners do not own the personally identifiable information they collect and provide such information only to GOLD’S GYM (or its designee) and to the delivery services (e.g., the U.S. Postal Service and UPS) they use to deliver merchandise that you order from the GOLDSGYM.COM shopping services. However, as authorized by GOLD’S GYM, our shopping partners will provide personally identifiable information in response to legitimate subpoenas or other appropriate law enforcement activities.

Credit card information provided to buy merchandise is used solely to determine that your card is valid, that sufficient credit is available to pay for the purchase and to apply the cost of your purchase to your card when the items are shipped. Credit card information you provide is transmitted across the Internet securely using encryption from your browser to our shopping partners’ secure order processing systems. Some versions of browsers and firewalls do not permit connection to secure servers. In such cases, you will not be able to connect to the server and therefore won’t be able to place an order through a secure connection. While no method is completely impenetrable, our shopping partners utilize state-of-the-art encryption technology used in e-commerce today. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, while our shopping partners are committed to protecting your personal information, they cannot entirely ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to them.

Please be aware that GOLDSGYM.COM advertisers or Web sites that have links on our Web site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to GOLDSGYM.COM are not covered by this privacy policy.

External Service Providers. There are a number of separate services offered by third parties that we refer to as external service providers that may be complimentary to your use of the Web site (e.g. merchandise providers, shipping, packaging). If you choose to use these separate services, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. We do not disclose your personal information to external service providers unless you provide your explicit consent. With your consent we may provide some of your personal information to the external service provider offering such services, for your convenience. To prevent our disclosure of your personal information to an external service provider, you can decline such consent or simply not use their services. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services. Users who register on a Gold’s Gym co-branded Web site grant Gold’s Gym permission to pass your email address back to that co-branded Web site. The use of your email address by the co-brand Web sites is limited by their applicable privacy policies.

Internal Service Providers for Our Operations. We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced Gold’s Gym related operation, unless you have explicitly agreed or given your prior permission to them for additional uses. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as for Gold’s Gym surveys or for a co-branded credit card). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all additional information you provide them and their additional uses will be strictly up to you. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your personal information is governed by their applicable privacy policy. Note that you might be on a mailing list for one or more of our independent franchised gym operators, so please contact them directly to remove your name from local mailing lists.

**SECURITY**  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, GOLDSGYM.COM cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use reasonable efforts to ensure that collected personally identifiable information is secure and not readily accessible to unapproved individuals or third parties. GOLDSGYM.COM has limited the number of people who have physical access to our database servers and has implemented electronic security systems and password protections which help further guard against unauthorized access.

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Web site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding GOLD’S GYM’s privacy policy and/or practices, write us at:

Gold’s Gym  
Matt Holder  
Director of Digital Marketing  
4001 Maple Ave., Suite 200  
Dallas, TX 75219

This policy, like the online medium itself, is subject to change and, as such, we encourage you to review this policy from time to time.

Effective Date: 06/02/2014
